const quizData = [
  {
    question: "What is the primary focus of Meter Group's business?",
    options: [
      "Financial consulting",
      "Agricultural technology",
      "Healthcare services",
      "Automotive manufacturing",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Agricultural technology",
  },
  {
    question: "In which year was Meter Group founded?",
    options: ["1995", "1983", "2002", "2010"],
    correctAnswer: "1983",
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the headquarters of Meter Group located?",
    options: [
      "Berlin, Germany",
      "Tokyo, Japan",
      "Pullman, Washington, USA",
      "New York, USA",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pullman, Washington, USA",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What environmental measurements and solutions does Meter Group provide?",
    options: [
      "Space exploration and rocket propulsion",
      "Fashion design and clothing manufacturing",
      "Soil moisture, climate, and plant science",
      "Cybersecurity and network management",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Soil moisture, climate, and plant science",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Meter Group's weather station product?",
    options: [
      "WeatherMax",
      "ZEN Meter",
      "ZL6",
      "Entertainment and gamingAquaSense",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "ZL6",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the original name of METER Group, Inc. when it was founded in 1983?",
    options: [
      "METER Environment",
      "Decagon Devices, Inc.",
      "METER Research",
      "METER Group, Inc.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Decagon Devices, Inc.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which environmental parameter is METER Group, Inc. most known for measuring and monitoring?",
    options: [
      "Sound intensity",
      "Solar radiation",
      "Soil moisture",
      "Air pressure",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Soil moisture",
  },
  {
    question: "In what country did METER Group, Inc. start its operations?",
    options: ["Japan", "United States", "Germany", "Australia"],
    correctAnswer: "United States",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the flagship product of Meter Group for soil measurement?",
    options: ["AquaCheck", "SoilSentry", "EcoProbe", "Teros"],
    correctAnswer: "Teros",
  },
  {
    question:
      "METER Group, Inc. specializes in environmental measurement solutions. What is the name of their soil moisture measurement technology?",
    options: ["TDR (Time Domain Reflectometry)", "RADAR", "SONAR", "LIDAR"],
    correctAnswer: "TDR (Time Domain Reflectometry)",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the key benefit of using METER Group's soil moisture sensors for agriculture?",
    options: [
      "Improving air quality",
      "Reducing carbon emissions",
      "Enhancing Wi-Fi signal strength",
      "Optimizing irrigation and water management",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Optimizing irrigation and water management",
  },
];

export default quizData;
